It's just to item eight, which is new business again, any new business?
We'll be able to do that and you'll know how many more things that students get to come to be and actually
will be like these for them and just help them extract their knowledge a little bit more to
and that like there's been more high enough that people that have that in place.
And this is the improvement for the pocket, the city loans, but they're doing it there, Expand.
There's been actually that that's going to be there for so that they would be a chartered up and so many that were that.
So it's definitely going to be a little harder than what that.
It's still improvement in the pocket we have.
It's improved to the partners, also improved to the program.
It's getting far because of the business, the market, mobile program.
They'll be really bad at practice and all that, whether it might be this.
Well that'd be a high school.
The school only though it has access to it since it's there.
There's so many other things that they don't have access to.
There's not an action item, so you just things make it so weird.
I think it's a lot of what we've got to walk through the school.
I don't know how to staff reports.
They're pretty, unfortunately, you're packet of available.
If there are any questions, staff's available.
Item 2, spare and counsel announcements.
Man, you all brought up the, do a re-ing in all of this.
The next one is the hall of England, which I think is the day I played the department.
The school that starts from around here in the sea island and no one orders that.
To talk about that day is the awful re-ing in which we'll be out of the line, activities that are on the exit.
That's what it is.
And that's what it's called.
And it's called.
And that's the University of High-knowledge.
One of the things so next week is our military schedule work session.
I'm going to be out of town, no need to go on the meat.
But if not, then we'll just wait and cancel that.
and I know it's been some conversation about project related to the railroad and other economic development projects.
It originally thought we would take that up at that meeting but I'd like to do that in a work session time environment.
So we'll do that in March if that's fine with everybody.
Okay.
So that in the other announcements.
I am a city manager communication student.
Okay.
Item 12 is exactly a session.
Person of the 25 OS 307B1.
I want to read the whole thing.
It's item number 12.
Do we have a motion to go in to exactly a session for the reasons again?
You do.
Okay.
And do we have a second?
Second.
Roll call, please.
Johnson.
Western.
All right.
Loose.
I'm more aster.
All right.